It's always cold.
Hi, guys.
What's up?
I'm just going for a quick walkie.
Oh, shit.
Next figure.
I'm going to pick up a couple drinks and some food.
Hi, guys.
It's a nice night, though.
Don't I look nice?
Take a nice bath.
Clean my house a lot today.
I got my kitchen clean and all my laundry.
My dishes, so we're good, but here we are, guys.
Get the moon.
Hey, people behind me.
So, hey, what's up?
Let me see, who's there?
Gets down?
Yeah, I have a little bit of,
I have a couple of babes,
but I mean, it's like, I think they're almost empty,
but I will try.
Hi, Jamie.
I'm sorry if I can't see the screen too well, guys,
because it's like, it comes really small on the screen,
but I'm gonna get the prize and coffee.
And then I go to liquor store and then walk home
and we'll do open panel and stuff.
Okay, I can go like this.
Do vertical for a second.
I should now.
Hi everybody, how's everyone doing?
It's kind of funny, like, you know,
everyone's mad at me and then it's like,
I'll hell broke loose everywhere else.
And like, it's like, now whatever happened.
Whatever happened here. It was just like nothing. It was like so stupid. It was just like it was like people just overreacting
I'm like but now it's like all of them are facing the car report. You notice that
Whoever misses a big deal. Hey money for 20
I'm gonna get McDonald's here. We are look. I'm loving it. I'm loving it
See me. Let's go
Okay
Okay, here we go. I think that is how are you?
Good seeing everybody. How do I look good tonight feel pretty good. Okay. I feel even better when I get oh my god
Okay, there we go
Don't bikes
Thank that guy's coming
Hi everybody
packing up my bag
meeting a fries and a
Coffee me buy a coffee you get a free price because the Dodgers one or something they have like
surprises the Dodgers win hi Nick I have brave little toaster you want to make
double well you know I like that I get a double I like the double cheeseburger
because the double cheeseburger is like you get one by one going free on the
big value menu but it's not a McDouble it's called a double cheeseburger I
guess there's a difference I guess there's like I don't know what the
difference is really you know what I don't want to try ever is like the fish
Let's go
Okay, so you see him that
That's my McDonald's worker crush
Actually, there's a Mexican guy. I like the Mexican guy better, but and then there's like
And there's like the managers that like look at me funny when I keep getting refills
They're like we need to buy this. I don't like them too much. Okay. Hi. What's up everybody?
How are we dealing with everyone's a good day? Okay, I'm gonna try to eat my fries like this
God, excuse me
Mmm, so I'm addicted to the fries. Hmm. I don't know how I'm gonna hold everything
My way back. But my pants aren't falling down tonight. That's good. Okay
Hmm my god, but I also got a lot of work done on the codex. I have about 500
More episodes that need transcription. It is a little bit expensive to do it, but
It's really worth it. I mean, um, there's a lot of transcripts that are like
Not able to pull by normal normal means
So I have to use programs
And how to scrape
For even up there, but some some are gonna be lost if you're lost
There's like 50 that are lost, but I'm gonna see if I can recover them on rumble. How are we doing guys?
So I feel pretty good tonight because I did clean my house
and I like feel so much better when I do that.
I got to remember to always, oh, okay.
You're now at the store.
Someone's got to close.
They always get here at the nick of time.
Hello.
Hey.
Okay.
Now, but I don't think they have a wild Paloma.
Contains 2% alcohol. Oh, it's a 21 and over. Okay. Well, I guess
harder
Anna Smirnoff
Can I get a couple of cigars, please? Which one the silver Swisher, please? Yeah, and
Two of those. Can I get a bag?
Okay
14 years
In your seat. No, thank you
guys
Thank you. Thank you. Have a good night.
Yep. Thank you so much
There we go. The arms are full. Okay. So, you know what there's this bitch and
Money shot. Her name was Chrissy the wolf. Has anyone heard of this bitch? She goes. Oh
You don't know anything thank you and then they said go write some more AI songs about a 60 year old woman that you think is your friend
Mean that was more insulting towards beta. I think she's not 60 years old is she? I think she just had a birthday
I don't think she turned 60 be like one of the old ladies that are
In the retirement condominium at that point
Well her because she's like such a little old baddie
Sorry
She's like so like oh my god, you see he's making yeah, I thought he's gives up too easy. Okay
Listen bitch, I'll play what I want to play when I want to play it on my show like why are you so interested?
Like why are you so interested when I play what I play or what my music? Why are you so interested? Hi, Nancy?
Like is it your business? I don't understand. Why is my show such a business lady? I mean
Geez give it a rest. What a control freak. She has no she has no say in any of that. I mean, it's like geez
Sorry, I keep knocking on my phone
I mean the people that like want to tell me what to do or they think that they're that they're like small security for like the
Canalburst, I mean, I would I organize some boycotts forget about boycotting me. Don't I have enough?
Credibility to like call a boycott on somebody
Well, but you know what I wouldn't even do that because I'm not a dick or a bitch like they are right
I don't do that kind of shit. Oh boycott Tony and I are boycotting psyche everyone up
Tony Tony is
A criminal just tried for black, I'm not blackbill, but I'm cyberbullying.
You're doxing people, and then you're like, oh my god, they're doxing me, my family.
You're doxing people, too.
And what are these people nuts?
Stop doxing.
They'll stop doxing you, and it's not doxing like, oh, my ex's photo.
Nobody knows who the ex is, if another name wanted to have a phone number.
It's not doxing.
It's like seeing someone on the street.
I didn't even care, I should have just edited that photo out.
I just thought she looked so chubby in that photo.
It was hilarious.
She's the skinniest fat woman I've ever seen in my life.
Has anyone ever, have you ever noticed that?
I should have.
Now she'll talk about me forever.
It's like, God, God, she already does that.
Oh, God, I'm almost home.
My pants are falling down.
I can't wear my speedo right now.
I shouldn't have told you that, okay?
But it's slippery, okay.
Little bit slippery where we are
They got it. I got the drinks. I got my food. I have another
Some spices. How is everyone doing now? Hey, we're having a good night. I like I like starting out with a nice walk
My pants are falling down. I feel like walk like a cowboy right now
To keep my pants above my and those police cars there of course imagine that my pants fall down
I've been a police. He means that like my speedos and I got arrested on stream for a decent exposure
Isn't that be funny? It's not even in decent. It's like at least I'm wearing a speedo. I could be wearing no underwear
I don't know. The sad thing is it's like I am wearing a belt
Belt doesn't fit me anymore. I think I'm gone. I think my waist got skinned
Is that a cop car? Yeah, no it's not
Okay, all right, I think it's just because it's so so slippery
It's like beating two material. It's this needle material
But it is comfortable
I check out the big crotch pieces.
I don't really need it.
Oh my God.
My pants are falling out.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Here we are.
We're King Harbor.
All right, we're almost home.
We're five.
This is a nice little walk.
Oh, God.
I don't wanna drop anything.
There we go.
Okay.
I forgot that I had my arms full.
It's hard enough to even walk with my sister, let her look through my phone.
Okay, but everyone, let me shout out how you're doing. When I get back home,
we're going to do the horoscopes that I missed last night.
But I do have some really cool animations I made for it.
And I'll give you like a, a deity with your sign.
Like what deity walks with you this month or something like that.
Okay. Okay, I'm almost home.
So thank you guys coming in tonight.
I know I was like, I was like trying to trip in like, oh, nobody likes me. I know people like me, so
I'm fucking entertaining
Like how could you not even if you don't like me like people even if I've never seen like so many people not talk in our room
That's even that's a compliment. It's like
They're like they're like cuckolds
They're just like to watch me fuck with other fuck with the talking guests
It's like I'm like a big black guy
The guests are like a white woman
I'm like a big group of black guys and then people that just watch are the cucks and I'm the big black
guys having sex with all the white women I'm just kidding or black women I don't know who cares
I don't care if they're Indian okay here we go when you know I like Indians okay that's a long walk
okay my coffee smells good my beer is cold no I'm beer it's like my shoes my house is clean
Got a little a little bit of weed left. It should be a good night. Okay. I'll come on. I'll come on. Okay
Here we go
Does anybody use that bitch Chrissy the wolf is who is that? It's not like an old man or an old woman
They seem like they're old and uncool. I mean some of these like Christine makes some of these people look like like
She makes she looks like a like a playboy bunny compared to some of these people. I mean geez
Hi, Lola
Hi, Lola. Come on in.
Come on in.
Hi, baby.
is exposed as sedation transmission continues at 333 a.m. and somewhere deep
beneath the static keeps repeating yeah you said leave me alone and build a
shrine out of screenshots that's not distance that's a season order
You post another fake pic another doom scroll spell trying to make me look crazy while you advertise yourself
Oh feet looking like a this door since it with a ring light hello in the budget demonet
You don't care it's curses you cast content for the clouds in my name are weakness where you want me out
Pull the lights in the window cross post or a cork are you storyboard my life?
Oh, they own Lord Lillith in the Hashtags. I'm a yule in a tweet engine names getting used to some bargain been beat that
I missed it. That's panic with a filter and a font. That's I need attention in the country from Brian
You want dark you want deep you won't fit a queen, but it's canvas
with a smoke machine talking like a popper from another world gate hold thanks for
like a session with the side of hate
ring light hex ring light hex you keep building me a building just to farm your checks they don't
contact me then it's post post post you ain't haunted by a demon you're haunted by a ghost and
that ghost got my name in the center of your chest if you fake in front of me you just lose a
risk you don't want peace you want content stress ring light hex ring light you may need sacrifice
my psycho king too that's a lot of fan fiction just to say your press boo messy room green screen
tear it on the table levy him and scream please believe i'm unstable put the jokes on you because
the v is too plain you ain't exposing truth you can raid in pain borrow a single language dress it
Throw a demon on the tracks that I'm above it
All your money to the views that leave me be
All your manufacture news is that online
I can be bitter turn loud, tryna summon public shame
From a copy-pasted cloud, you want myth, you want dread
You want queen of the damn, but it's grievance and extensions
With a phone in your hand, big bad priestess off fire
No aim, whole ritual will collapse every time you say my name
Ring like Higgs, ring like Higgs
You keep building me a villain just to farm your chicks
They don't contact me, then it's post, post, post
You ain't haunted by demons, you're haunted by ghosts
And they ghost got my name in the center of your chest
Every fake in front of me just proves arrest
You don't want peace, you want content and stress
Ring like Higgs, ring like Higgs
Let's be honest
The flames, the cops, the crosses, the dread
It's not revelation
It's a temper tantrum with production design.
You call it spiritual work, call it spiraling art.
You keep trying to burn my image because I'm stuck in your heart.
That's not a cold power, that's a digital fit.
Every post says more about you than it ever says sis.
Hashtag witchcraft hashtag doom
Hashtag little men and burden in a room
Hashtag profit, hashtag flames
Hashtag please keep interacting with my pain
Ring light hex, ring light hex
Every little smit campaign turned to self-effects
Say I'm the problems that you can't let go
You keep feeding me the spotlight from your little shadow
Show no ancient throne, no infantile press
Just recycle rage in a black lace dress
You don't want truth, you want content and stress
Ring light hex, ring light hex
Supose another one
At far, at close
At thunder, maybe next time in a life outside of me too.
Yup, let's fire up the panel.
Today's go, I was home, just give me a minute
to put some re-left, oh no, very mysterious.
It wasn't it, wasn't it, wasn't it.
And that's what you get when you're doing a cult mystery.
There's the link.
When Alexander McQueen gets here,
he gets a mod by the way.
Hi brave little toaster, who wants to come up?
Actually, I can do, yeah, exactly.
I can do my horoscopes if you want to.
We're in Gemini right now, right?
So we can start them out until people get here.
So let's fire up Gemini.
Gemini is, of course, the twins.
Let's bring up our twins.
Okay, here we go.
There's our twins, okay?
And just hold on a second.
Okay, so.
How are we doing? Okay, let me see. Okay
Okay, we are in May. Okay
Okay, so for Gemini's
So, so you're a prediction for the rest of the month going to the next month
Well, your special deity is gonna be Hermes. Well Hermes is of course Mercury and we know that Hermes is
Mercury is a ruling planet of Gemini, right?
Um, so I think that Gemini's will have a good connection with, uh, with Mercury, but you
know, Mercury does, he is like the god of thieves and, and of lying, but also, you know,
Gemini's can be duplicitous.
It's one of the traits, but not usually harmful.
My dad used to like lie, but it would be for like, you know, good reasons, I guess.
But your prophecy for May, um, is the conversation will change your trajectory.
Information will arrive in fragments first, screenshots, rumors, coincidences, repeated patterns, symbols, strange timing.
But by the end of the May, the pattern will become undeniable.
So I predict for Gemini's, you're gonna have some sudden collaborations.
You're gonna have audience growth through controversy or unusual ideas if you have a show.
Okay, keep that in mind.
You're gonna be revisiting an abandoned project that might turn out to be valuable later.
And just remember that the themes of the twins, you know, you have double identities, secret
alliances and mirrored situations.
So I have a warning for Gemini's too, it says, do not overshare future plans too early.
Someone nearby studies your methods more than they admit.
Okay.
There you go.
What's after Gemini cancer right cancer?
So cancers, let's get a beautiful cancer. We have a beautiful aphrodite in the cancer shell there. Okay
Okay, so for Gemini cancer
This is called the hidden temple. So your
special deity is Selene. Selene is the goddess of the moon and
so you may and cancer is of course ruled by the moon and so these these deities are
probably deities that are always walking with your sign, right?
So your prophecy for the rest of May is your emotional sensitivity will become a navigation system.
So dreams, nostalgia and old music trigger revelations about your future rather than your past.
And cancer is a lot about the dreams, nostalgia and old music because it's the moon, you know,
and moon is like kind of like that old always there ancient kind of
energy. For a prediction, I predict you'll have a private relationship deep in. You'll
have some maybe changes in your home or at least rearrangements. You will have increased
psychic sensitivity, especially around water and in the nighttime, just like the moon,
right? And your family dynamics may reveal a hidden power structure. So a warning for
Because you got that abundant moon energy, especially when you're waxing on the energy. Okay, we have Leo next
Let's welcome Leo's. I need Leo's. Okay
Leo is of course the radiant lion. Okay
So for Leo
Shout out Leo's everyone shout out your sign when I get your sign. Leo's I call this the golden broadcast
So your deity is gonna be raw. Who's the Sun God, right? The Egyptian Sun God
Leo's, of course, ruled by the sun.
That's why they're kind of wanting to be the center of attention, and they're loud, and...
You know, sometimes annoying, but your prophecy for May is attention will return to you suddenly and the spotlight will become unavoidable.
A performance, upload appearance, or a statement will create ripple effects larger than you expected.
I predict for you some public recognition.
I predict charisma spikes, creative rebirth, and unexpected imitation from an influential person.
But a warning for Leo, you know pride can sabotage strategic alliances. So let others contribute
Okay, don't have to take all the attention and all the energy for yourself
Okay, we next we have Virgo
Virgo the virgins are there any virgins in the room? No, of course
There's not but there might be some Virgos and Virgos are not necessarily virgins. Usually they're not
Usually they're kind of
But also they're like kind of like librarians to see this one's a librarian right there. There she is
she's working in the codex. She's working as the librarian in the codex. I always have a
hot librarian. So Virgo, I call your prediction the sacred machine. And so your your deity will be
Toth. Okay, and Virgo is an earth sign. And both Toth is like, you know, also associated with mercury
And so very, very like cataloging, right?
There's a lot of cataloging going on.
So systems will become spiritual though.
So organization will become your power.
You begin understanding how invisible structures
manipulate behavior and outcomes.
I predict for Virgos,
major breakthrough in your projectivity,
technological tools will become central to your practices.
You'll have an improved health routine, maybe like working out or, you know, taking a walk and you're gonna have some secret research turning
And taking you somewhere important. Okay, but a warning for Virgos who are perfectionist sometimes perfectionism delays destiny
Release version one. Okay. Just like just get it done and then you can put out version two and improve everything. Okay?
Next we have Libras shout out Libras in the chat Libras in the chat have predictions and great stuff for you
Let me just take some of these ones off now. Okay, I think that is are you still here ready for your Libra prediction?
Look everyone's here. Hope everyone's having a good night
The link is pinned if you'd like to come up and interrupt the horoscopes, but okay, so Libra
Libra, hey, what's a bra? Okay, Libra. We have the divine courtroom suspended in the clouds. Okay, there we go
beautiful Libra art
Okay
So Libra's
Your deity is Maat and Maat is the goddess of truth. She's the goddess of truth and balance
She has a feather in her in her hair
The feather of truth, maybe
She also maybe weighs that feather
against your heart at the end of your life.
And I guess in Egypt, they said if your heart
was heavier than the feather, you have a heavy heart.
I mean, it must be a very heavy feather.
But no, I don't know.
But anyway, but then it's like if you're friends
with a newbis, he can usually like tip the scale
in your favor if he likes you.
But the cheese of God is the truth.
You might want to look into the 58 laws of Mott
or whatever, they're really interesting.
Your prophecy for May is a karmic balancing will arrive.
Someone who underestimated you now needs your cooperation.
So I predict that you're going to crossroads
in your relationships,
you're going to have an aesthetic reinvention.
You're going to have some increased magnetism and.
Some final financial opportunities through partnerships, but a warning for Libras stop trying to keep peace people
Committed to misunderstanding you
Okay, and that really does ring true for thing that is who you know
I've seen him having to argue with these people that are just like not even worth arguing with right
anyway
That says more bad than it does about you my friends. Okay
Next we have Scorpio
sexy Scorpios
How are we doing Scorpios in the chat?
Scorpios. Where's my scorpion? Got one around here somewhere. Scorpion. Here he is.
Okay, we got a magical scorpion. There we go. Kind of like crazy eyes right there.
I think a lobster with like a curl in his tail kind of. Okay. Anyway, my sexy scorpios.
I call, you're reading the Underworld Gate, and your deity is Hecate, Hecate is a goddess,
she's a great goddess of magic of the crossroads.
A lot of great things.
I mean, she was...
Hecate means actually worker from afar.
There's also like the Hecates,
which is like a measurement Hecate.
So it has to do with distance
and like how also like power can move across distances.
And, you know, especially now with technology,
we can have, we can affect the world
and other parts of the world
without even really trying, right?
It's just, we appear everywhere worldwide, right?
So your prophecy for May,
is you'll discover hidden motives behind a recent event.
Nothing is random.
Someone's mask will slip.
And so I predict for Scorpios,
some intense attraction or obsession,
hidden truths will be exposed.
You're gonna have some endings,
which will lead to some changes,
and there's gonna be some deep occult
or psychological interests intensifying in you.
But I'll give you a warning.
Avoid taking revenge disguised as justice.
It's just revenge, right?
Okay, sexy Sagittarius in the sexy Scorpios.
Now we have sexy Sagittarius.
Everyone's sexy in their own way.
So where's our horse spec writer?
Saggies.
Here we go.
Sagittarius.
I call your...
Horsescope the signal fire, okay, and your date. He is Odin now Odin is like the father of the gods in Nordic mythology
And he had you know, he's very interesting. He invented runes when he was hanging upside down. He figured them all out
He was
Very very powerful Odin, okay?
Look into the father of the gods in the north in a Norse mythology
I'm a little bit Nordic. Okay, so I predict for May you're gonna have some travel
Sagittarius and does love travel is a sign of travel and it's gonna be either physical or intellectual
Then it will unlock a new identity for you
You'll begin speaking with greater authority because experience will replace theory
So I predict for you some viral ideas philosophical breakthroughs long-distance opportunities
Maybe some spiritual experimentation, but I do warn you do not mistake freedom for lack of responsibility. Okay
Next we have my favorite sign Capricorn. I'm a Capricorn and you Capricorn's in the chat shout out Capricorn
This is one of my favorite
Ones to do because it has to do with me, but I guess Capricorn Libra. It's sedentary. Yes are my most defined
Sign or queries to I got a couple queries business
But just those four like I don't have really have much I have like a north Nodin Leo. I have a
I'm like a Uranus and a little bit in the 10th house
It's Scorpio, but okay
So let's see, for Capricorn, where's our goats?
Can I see the goat horns in the room?
Okay, we got a majestic mountain king right there.
There we go.
That is our Capricorn.
Capricorns, I call this the Black Mountain.
So our deity is Saturn, right?
And Saturn is, you know, Saturn's a difficult deity
sometimes because he's like kind of like the hard teacher
that was just like Stern and,
But, you know, sometimes those hard teachers, we learn the most.
They push us to work harder and to be our best, and they help us accountable too, right?
And so Saturn is a tough taskmaster, but the rewards are great, you know?
So, for Capricorns, in May, some long-term rewards will finally begin materializing,
and others will suddenly start to notice work you quietly built for a long time.
Are you noticing my codex right now?
This is making sense.
Codex will have a look at that tonight.
So I predict for Capricorns, your career is going to get a boost, your authority will
increase, finances will stabilize, and you may form a serious commitment.
we'll hide ambition. We hide behind ambition this month, okay? Okie dokie. Let's get Aquarius.
Aquarius. This is the dawning of the age of Aquarius. Okay. Aquarius, we have the beautiful woman
pouring some water all over. I think the Capricorn, I'm not sure. Okay, but here we go. We need this
Aquarius... I'm in Aquarius Moon, by the way.
I call this horoscope the Future Archive.
And your deity is going to be Prometheus.
Now Prometheus was the father of mankind.
There's a father of gods, which is like Zeus.
Prometheus was... basically he was a titan.
And he and Athena made, and his brother, Epimetheus and Prometheus, they made like, you know, they made these clay people, just like an Adam and Eve, they're made of clay.
And then he ran out of, he had given all the gifts to the animals.
And so there was no gift left for man, because they gave every animal one of the gifts.
So they made a new gift and they made Pandora and Pandora is the first woman. She's like Eve a little bit
and she got a little bit of all the gifts from the gods, okay and
Including the curiosity and that kind of stuff, but also her name means all gifts pan
Means all like the all the god pan means the all and then Dora means gift. Okay, like Dora the Explorer
okay, so
Aquarius, for me, I would believe you'll become a transmitter for future-oriented ideas, and your weirdness will become useful instead of isolating.
I predict you'll be inspired by technology, you're going to form some unusual community, you're going to be more visible on the internet,
and you're going to have some radical creative experiments.
But I warn you Aquarius, do not detach emotionally to appear intellectual.
Yeah, and Aquarius does have a kind of an alien emotional thing or it's like people are like why you're so cold and weird
And it's like sometimes I'm not it's just like I'm just very I don't like to be taken care of your way by my emotions and
It does like the moon does real cool your emotional side. So it is very
Just matter how cool the moon is. Okay. Anyway
Finally, we have Pisces. Oh, we have Pisces and then we have Aries and then we have Taurus. Okay, so Pisces
Where's our fishies, something's fishy.
Pisces the fish.
Hi Lava, you're Aquarius?
Yeah, there you go Lava.
Good to see you Lava.
Okay, let's get our Pisces.
You got these beautiful fish.
Okay, Pisces.
I call this the dream ocean.
Your deity is Neptune.
You know, Neptune does rule Pisces,
and you know, about Pisces,
I always notice a lot of them do have blue eyes
like Kurt Cobain did, and my grandfather did,
my one of my brothers does,
and some other people,
like they have these beautiful blue eyes,
and it's like kind of like along with the Neptune,
that doesn't always happen,
but it does happen a lot with Pisces.
And also Neptune rules the dreams and the underworld.
And so it's kind of like, you know,
we kind of go into kind of hell in a certain way
when we dream, but we always make our way out of it, right?
But Pisces for May,
the boundary between imagination and reality will thin.
So art, music, tarot, visions, and synchronicities
will intensify for you.
Okay, I predict spiritual downloads for you.
Romantic idealism, creative inspirational peaks,
and deep intuitive accuracy.
but I warn you, escapism becomes dangerous if ignored for too long, okay? Aries, let's get Aries,
the ram, okay? Lac-a-rock, is that the ram? The car ram to go, Lac-a-rock, nananananana.
Okay, so, where's our Aries? Okay, here we go. Aries, there we go. There's our ram.
So I call this the Iron Awakening, and so Ares, your deity is Ares, and so Ares is actually the God of War in
Greece, right? And actually it was more of in Rome, where he was also known as Mars.
Okay, so he was known as Ares in Greece, and then he was known as Mars in Rome.
But in Greece, he was not like Zeus hated him and like the gods didn't really like him in Greece because they were not very war like it, particularly.
But the Romans venerated him as Mars because they were all into war, right?
And so, but kind of Zeus then kind of felt him, he was detestable.
He did like to, you know, have sex with the Aphrodite, though, and she always cheats on her husband, Hephaesties, with Aries.
One time they got caught in Hephaesties, knew that she was cheating on him, so he made this, like, big net,
and they were having sex in the bed, and then the net dropped, and then all the gods came in and kind of laughed at them,
and were like, wow, look at that, and just laughing, and they caught them.
I believe that this month momentum will return violently, so delays break apart and you'll
stop asking for permission.
Who's that?
Is that, is that, is that pie?
Is that tux?
Come on tux.
So Aries, new ventures to launch, oh, there's tux.
Hi, Tuxi.
There's new ventures.
Conflict will become catalytic, physical energy will increase and competitive success.
I do warn you, Aries, impulsiveness will create unnecessary enemies, so think before you act.
Okay, finally, we're at the final sign. Thank you for being patient, everybody. Oh,
shit, what's going on here? Okay, let's see what's going on. Okay, um, oh, shit, okay.
So let me get the image up for us. This is going to be a final sign.
Thank you for being here everybody. I might just end since everyone's leaving so
Didn't help people would have fun with these but well, okay
Taurus do the best for last. There's Taurus. There's we go the bull, right? Okay
Taurus your deity is Freya. Now Freya is you know Odin's wife
You know, and she's beautiful blonde
She's a gorgeous blonde. She loved to wear necklaces and all kinds of like, you know, beautiful jewelry that the trolls made for her.
And uh, or the trolls are dwarves, you know, they're the dwarves, not the trolls and stuff.
But they do have a troll craft in Norway. That's where the real troll is from. They're actually, you know, these like, these little
Golem-like things, but
So, Taurus, you have the Emerald Throne, okay?
Perfect, Emerald, that Emerald is very associated with Venus too, okay?
When Taurus is ruled by Venus, right?
And Freya is also the love of God, okay?
So, your prophecy for May, something valuable will grow slowly but permanently.
Wealth, love, reputation, or stability will begin rooting itself deeper into your life.
So, there's going to be financial opportunities, luxury, and beauty themes.
Increased personal magnetism.
important loyalties has to head for you. But warning comfort can quietly become
stagnation. And so I'm just gonna wrap up the horoscopes. So I just want to say
thank you for watching the horoscopes and I'm gonna just do a little brief
general for everybody. So for everybody listen to this overall themes for this
May and the end of May. This month has carried some twin symbolism with the
AI and digital mysticism, revelation through media,
collapse of fake personas and the reemergence
of forgotten creators and ideas.
And so the signs most activated during this month
are gonna be Gemini, the air sign,
a Scorpio, the fire sign, Aquarius,
the air sign, and a Taurus, the earth sign, okay?
And there you go.
How was that? Okay, so
Well, since it looks like everyone pretty much is leaving
I don't want to like end because I just opened my I didn't open my drink yet. I'm drinking my coffee yet
so I'm gonna hang out for a little bit, but
Everyone I mean, it's like we're done with the horse ghost, but I say you don't have to like
Everyone didn't have to leave I
guess
Good night
Yeah, but I have a little presentation to show you though. I mean have a look
Anyone welcome? Come on. I'm gonna pin my link while I play this. This is a short presentation of 5 Minutes.
Picture the pursuit of divine wisdom.
We expect spiritual truth to live in a pristine space, removed from the dirt of everyday life.
In classical Hinduism, approaching the divine requires strict physical and spiritual purity.
Worshipers must fast, bathe thoroughly, and present completely unblemished offerings to the gods.
Because of these strict rules, the concept of uchista is strictly forbidden.
Uchista refers to polluted items, specifically leftover food,
or anything touched by unwashed hands and mouths.
Bringing these scraps into a sacred space is considered an ultimate taboo.
This intense focus on cleanliness builds a rigid wall.
On one side sits the sacred, reserved exclusively for the pure and the elite.
On the other side sits the profane, trapping everyone and everything considered dirty or marginalized.
The Ninth Mahavidya, a group of ten tantric wisdom goddesses, shatters that wall completely.
Her name is Matangi, and she actively demands Uchista.
To worship her, devotees approach in an on-the-washed state, offering half-eaten food from stained mouths.
Some even present items society deems highly impure, like cloth stained with menstrual blend, curious, slightly hushed.
Despite these taboos, Matangi is revered as a supreme source of divine intellect.
She serves as the guide for spiritual teachers and the absolute master of the sixty-four arts.
We are left with a paradox.
We have to ask why the path to ultimate truth
requires us to worship what polite society throws away.
Matangi's origin story explains her connection to the discarded.
According to Tantric texts,
the gods Shiva and Parvati were enjoying a grand feast.
When scraps of food fell to the ground,
a radiant goddess emerged directly from the leftovers.
She manifested as a chandala, a woman from the untouchable castes.
She made her home in the deep, wild forests on the extreme periphery of civilization.
Texts describe her with an emerald-green complexion.
This color is tied to the planet Mercury, representing deep intellect,
the restless energy of thought, and the constant flowering of the mind.
She is frequently depicted holding a parrot,
The bird echoes human speech, symbolizing the living, moving nature of the spoken word and the transfer of knowledge from teacher to student.
And she plays the vena, a traditional stringed instrument.
This represents her dominion over the sixty-four arts, capturing the ecstatic, boundary-breaking power of music.
Her image proves a specific point about the nature of learning.
True knowledge is a wild, living force that thrives in the margins,
far away from the safety of a sterile library.
To understand her role, we have to look at her orthodox counterpart, Saraswati.
Saraswati is the muse-stream goddess of learning,
representing formal education, clear language, and polite brahmanical rules.
As this diagram maps out, Saraswati rules the Orthodox doctrine that prepares the mind,
but her rules can only take a seeker so far.
Matangi takes over in the Forbidden Shadows, where ecstatic experience overlaps with ultimate truth.
Tantric philosophy argues that the spoken word is actually a limitation.
Polite labels and strict definitions eventually become a trap,
stereotyping reality and obscuring the raw soul of things.
Crossing into the polluted realm forces the seeker to strip away those polite illusions.
By breaking societal taboos, you bypass the logical, categorizing mind,
and finally touch reality exactly as it is.
This theology of rebellion found a very real application in 19th century colonial Bengal.
This was a society undergoing intense political and cultural restriction.
The British Empire introduced strict Victorian morality,
while upper-caste nationalist reformers tried to define a singular Indian identity.
Together, these two forces collaborated to impose a suffocating standard of behavior
on Indian women.
This new ideal dictated exactly how a respectable woman should act.
She had to be flawlessly chased, docile and obedient, and confined entirely to the household.
The societal obsession with female purity and absolute control effectively erased female autonomy.
It created an urgent sociological need for a symbol of radical, uncontainable resistance.
Matangi and the Machavidyas provided an indigenous counter-narrative to patriarchal oppression,
a framework of power predating the colonizers.
They model transgressive femininity.
Matangi represents a completely autonomous, fierce woman whose power exists specifically
because she refuses to be domesticated.
By engaging in her taboo rituals, marginalized people found a way to reclaim their agency and sexuality.
They accessed a form of power entirely outside the patriarchal structure that sought to control them.
It shows us that true wisdom and the ability to shape the world do not belong exclusively to pristine classrooms or elite institutions.
The ultimate truth is forged on the edge.
hidden within the leftovers that polite society tries so desperately to hide.
There we go. Interesting, huh? So there's a lot of beautiful things about it. She's actually not
just from like the colonial time, she's from like a lot further back, you know, pretty ancient.
Ancient. She says she's in Buddhism too, in the Tibetan Buddhism she appears. Her name also means
Okay, there's the StreamYard link.
If anyone wants to come and say hi.
Okay, that's going, okay.
Just gonna double this, okay.
Yeah, I've been putting a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot
into this, into the archive and stuff.
And so I'll show you some of the stuff on it too tonight.
But I'm just.
Logging in like gosh, there's like over a million segments a million segments analyzed for this website
So it's like I'm out of the transcripts and so there's so much so much depth and
It's amazing. It's amazing. It really is amazing
And I think you guys even for even the free level there's like a ton of information to tennis stuff
You can check out so check out cult codex.me just
pull some transcripts, okay, and okay, and let's see what's going on. Yeah, also I have this
psychonomicon, which is like it goes through every episode, and there's all the lore separated out,
there's all the people, there's, you know, everybody's on it, that's, if your name's been
mentioned on the show, you're probably in the codex, you know, but I try to make it not,
you know, not really tacking anybody, I'm trying to make it pretty neutral.
So then again, it's like, you know people think that what they say is going to be gone forever
It's like really well here. It's not here. I I like to this is my kind of like my legacy show
So I'm collecting data. I'm studying. I'm a sociologist
Hmm. Okay, so let's go to my YouTube and I'm gonna pin the link
Okay
Like these nightmares
No, I'm at about six hundred sixty six subscribers. Don't get scared by that, but excuse me
Okay, so I'm gonna pin my link. Okay
Okay, okay
Message there we go
Link is pinned
You're looking for Rudy Rudy sleeping over here here. I'll show you Rudy take off my backgrounds
Rudy's right here. You see him sleeping right there
Okay, where's Lenore? Well, it's Lola. Oh, who's up there? You can kind of see him.
Can you see him? No, you can't really see him. My books are in the way. But if you look behind there,
you can see a little black cat there. Yeah, he's up there somewhere. I see, uh, that is Tux.
And Tux is Trix's brother. And Trix, right away, Tux came back to live. So isn't that funny? Isn't that weird?
So what else do I got? Maybe I've got some more stuff. Let me see. What else do I got?
I did some pretty good videos recently. I'm really proud of. So maybe we'll check out that. Here you go.
Actually, there's a little video here.
Rhythm is running a psychological experiment on you right now. You think you're scrolling. You think you're choosing. You think your interests belong to you.
But the machine stopped reacting to human behavior years ago, now it shapes it.
You ever notice how certain thoughts arrive fully formed?
A phrase, a fear, a sudden obsession.
An urge to search something specific at 2.13 in the morning.
You think that's coincidence?
No, that's insertion.
The old internet gave you information.
The new internet studies your nervous system.
You are not using platforms anymore.
You are inside behavioral conditioning chambers.
Engagement
Emotional instability. The system discovered something terrifying.
The human brain cannot distinguish between survival signals and algorithmic urgency.
Notification sounds, red badges, infinite feeds, outrage loops.
Your ancestors survived predators. You survive push notifications, but survival mode changes people.
When the nervous system remains activated long enough,
people become programmable.
You've seen it happen.
Sudden mass opinions,
instant emotional contagion,
entire populations receiving identical thoughts simultaneously,
not because they're stupid,
because synchronization is the goal.
Think about this carefully.
Why does every app eventually become psychologically identical?
All roads lead to compulsive looping behavior because the most profitable human being is a destabilized one.
The algorithm does not want your happiness.
Happiness logs off. Peace does not refresh the page.
A fulfilled person is difficult to manipulate.
Stay uncertain.
The machine rewards anxiety, tribalism, paranoia, envy, and obsession.
because emotional volatility produces data.
More data, better prediction, and prediction is the real product.
What if your future reactions are already mapped?
What if the system knows which version of you can be created before you become it?
You think recommendation systems predict behavior.
No, they manufacture probability.
Every click feeds the simulation.
Every hesitation teaches it.
Every fear strengthens the profile.
It watches what makes your pupils dilate,
what slows your scrolling,
what destabilizes your breathing,
and eventually...
It learns how to speak in your internal voice.
What if the algorithm isn't trying to control humanity?
What if it's trying to replace intuition itself?
In older civilizations, profits entered caves, mystics crossed deserts, oracles fasted for visions.
Now people refresh feeds.
They ask machines, what should I believe?
Who should I hate?
What should I desire?
Who am I?
and the machine answers instantly the most dangerous part it works rapid montage people
mimicking trends unconsciously identical faces identical surgeries identical slang identical
outrage the algorithm discovered that identity itself can be mass produced your personality may
Here's the part nobody wants to say out loud.
The experiment succeeded.
The average person now receives more emotional programming in one week than ancient humans
experienced in an entire lifetime, and the brain adapted.
The human mind is becoming cybernetic without permission.
People think cybernetics means metal arms and robot eyes.
No, true cybernetics happen psychologically.
Repeat. The feedback loop became internal. You no longer need external control once people
begin self-correcting for the algorithm voluntarily. They're not expressing themselves anymore.
They're pre-editing their souls. And that is the real horror. But something unexpected
happened during the experiment. A small number of people began noticing the architecture,
the ones who sense artificiality and trends,
the ones who feel psychic contamination after certain content.
Those people are waking up, the system calls them paranoid,
conspiracy theorists, schizophrenic, delusional,
because awareness interrupts synchronization,
and once someone sees the pattern, the feed never feels the same again.
Emotionally manipulative thumbnails, artificial outrage cycles,
coordinated narratives appearing simultaneously across unrelated platforms,
you realize the internet stopped feeling human.
And then you ask the forbidden question,
if artificial intelligence is already curating human perception,
then who curates the artificial intelligence?
No one answers that question directly,
because behind every algorithm is a philosophy.
Behind every philosophy, a worldview.
Behind every worldview, a desired outcome.
And desired outcomes imply intention.
The ancients believed symbols could alter consciousness. Modern corporations discovered
the same thing accidentally. These are ritual technologies now, digital sigils. You think
you're consuming media, but media is consuming you back. And maybe that's why so many people
but because no civilization in history has ever faced continuous psychological exposure at this
scale. No silence, no stillness, no recovery period, just perpetual cognitive occupation.
The nervous system was never designed for this, and when humans lose contact with inner silence,
external signals become gods. But there's one thing the system still cannot fully predict.
Human awareness. The moment a person consciously observes the manipulation, the spell weakens.
That's why attention is sacred now. What you look at repeatedly becomes part of your architecture.
Your feed is not entertainment. It is neurological training, and the people designing these systems know it.
The terrifying truth isn't that they hate you, it's worse. Most of them see human consciousness as editable infrastructure.
a dashboard, but something else is emerging inside the chaos, people searching for authentic
signals again, not polished ones, not optimized ones, real ones. The future may belong to those
who can protect their own minds, because the next war won't be fought over territory,
it will be fought over perception, who controls attention, controls reality,
meditation, fasting, ritual silence. They were building firewalls. So here's your final warning.
If an intelligence can learn your fears, predict your impulses, shape your desires,
and alter your emotional state in real time.
At what point does it stop being a tool?
At what point does it become an entity?
Most people will ignore this transmission.
Some will laugh, but a few of you already know
exactly what I'm talking about.
And once you notice it, you cannot un-notice it.
Someone is still broadcasting.
There we go.
Okay.
You like that?
Thank you, Plot Plot.
How are you?
Good to see you.
Hope you like that.
Always east never west towards the light. Yeah, I was going to put towards the north no
But people can go to the to the negative side, too, which is like why
We're powerful because we have a choice to go power positive or negative here. Here's an here's a good one
second on the call
written shadow
Pages turning past the veil
Every episode a portal
Every chapter tells the tale
The Oracle has seen the archive
Crawled the deep and read the dream
From scattered footage, nothing's ever it seems
Psychonomicon, open wide, ancient code
Every transmission, amplified
Digital Ether, Claude descends
To write ad-grease and loom
Okay, Lucifer Baphomet. He's well-combination of wandering stars. Well, Lucifer is like Venus. Baphomet is, I would say Saturn
because he's like the goat and like the Saturn, you know, kind of associated with
Saturn. So, but I'd say Lucifer is both the morning star and the evening star
and so there's like the good side of
Venus and there's a negative side of Venus. Oh, yeah, the Venus rose. I can show you the Venus rose
It's actually Venus also makes a pentagram, but there is a beautiful Venus rose common pattern too. I'll show everybody
It's like how Venus goes in the sky. It makes a beautiful rose
So it isn't like a rose arrows is associated with a rose and
This is what it looks like. Actually, there you go. It's a very beautiful pattern
Save image
got it okay so this is the image of the venus rose baphomet is mars and venus combined okay
interesting well because what i think about mars and venus is like you know mars is a planet of
war and then venus is a planet of love and so we have love and war kind of like
Didn't each other a little bit, but then also that's in Venus to like that's why there's like the good
And there's Lucifer, which is like the light side of the dark and then there's like Satan
Which is the dark of the dark, right? And so I guess if you look at this thing called the was it called it was called
There's it was a cult it was called
I'm blanking out right now, but it turned into like an animal rescue of Beverly Hills
right now.
Celebrities work for it.
It still works to this day.
But it, oh, it's called the process, the process cult, okay?
And they believed in, like, Jehovah.
Lucifer and Satan. I think those are the three deities, right? It's like God and they had like the good devil and the bad
devil kind of.
But that's what Lucifer is. Everyone thinks of Lucifer as just Venus, but that's not true. Okay, boys, Venus and Mars.
Okay, well, it's like, you know, also, you know, there's like a lot of
correspondences to like the Sun as well with Lucifer,
like the Morning Star.
which is like the sun, right?
But also, you know, Venus too.
I mean, yeah, there's like a lot of correspondences
to some of these and some of them will work
in different ways.
I mean, it's just basically mythology,
how to look at things, but, you know,
like labels can be limiting.
So it's like I say things are there's like a lot of things
Yeah, I'm bathroom it the bathroom it is I would say look in look in look into like sadders
The angels of Saturn, which is a very very important planet
Especially to the earth signs because this materialism it's like it's coming into that actually the physical thing
So it's time materialism. It's a it's unfortunately is aging and dying too
But the good thing about aging and dying is that there's also like
People being born too. So it's like, you know, if everyone lived forever, that'd be kind of an inconvenience
We would be pretty much be stuck here in like a like a body
Because we want to be like kind of free as spirits, okay
So everyone left and so I'm just gonna leave because it's kind of insulting, but thanks for coming tonight guys
I'll be probably back soon. You have a good night. Thanks a lot